Finally... I'm so tired.
Oh, Inamori-san!
That's okay, I can unload it.
Nah, I'll take everything to your room.
Welcome back. Looks like you
were out until dark, huh?
I can take your bag.
I can take it myself!
More importantly, what time is it?
Let's see... just about seven.
Thanks. That's a nice time to start with.
Okay.
See you around.
When She's Upset the Rain Falls
and the Dark Night Descends
Excuse me, have you seen Yoshino?
She's got summer lessons at school,
and I thought I'd attend with her.
I think Sota gave her a ride to school.
Inamori-san took her?
Yoshino!
Hey there.
I heard Inamori-san brought
you to... school...
You mentioned wanting to get a
parfait yesterday, right?
Wanna grab one later?
Did you understand the lesson today?
Should I explain anything?
It's supposed to rain in two days.
You mentioned wanting to air out your futon,
so you should probably do that tomorrow.
Um, is something wrong, Yoshino?
Can you hear me?
Welcome home, you two.
I just got back!
Thanks for giving me the
early lift this morning.
Oh, it's fine. I'm up at five anyway.
I see you came home with Kirishima-san.
No, I came home alone.
See ya.
Uh, Kirishima-san, did you do something?
You shut up and go.
We'll talk about this when
we're back in Tokyo.
Oh, dear.
And how exactly is she ignoring you?
I've rung the doorbell about a
hundred times in the last hour,
and she won't answer.
Oh my, you should definitely stop.
That's just splashing oil on the fire.
She really is mad, then?
I had kind of assumed that it
was all water under the bridge.
Absolutely not, considering
you brought knives into it.
From the sound of it, she really is mad,
but Yoshino-chan will calm down
after a set period she decides on,
so hang in there until then.
Do you have any idea how
long it's going to be?
Well, Shoma-kun would occasionally
seriously upset her and get ignored like this,
so it's probably best to just
watch out for 24 hours.
Hey, Tsubaki! Food's here.
Coming!
I'm on a date with Renji-san, so bye now!
Yoshino!
I made some food. Would you let me in?
You mentioned you like chikuwabu right?
Yoshino?
Excuse me, Inamori-san.
We've got powdered sugar and lemons, right?
Do you mind if I use them?
Sure, go ahead.
Yoshino! I made some madeleines.
You mentioned liking lemon custard, right?
Let's eat them together.
Sorry, Inamori-san, do we have
50 grams of mirror glaze,
some cocoa butter, and 100
grams of chocolate chips,
along with a large baking stone, a Brix
refractometer, and a mesh baking mat?
Seriously, Yoshino, open up!
I'm begging you! I made cake!
This is all my fault,
so let's just talk it over!
I think I'm going to die from not
being able to talk with you!
And it's been over 48 hours since.
What do you think?
I don't give a shit.
Uh, what exactly is all this?
Feel free to eat it before it goes bad.
She's still ignoring you, then?
Normally, she lets me in after an apology,
no matter how much I upset her.
This is awful...
You're creeping me out, kid.
Aren't you a masochist? Shouldn't
you enjoy this kind of thing?
I'll admit I was having a bit
of fun until this morning.
But just being left to twist like this,
with no idea when it'll end...
I start worrying that it might
keep up for over a month.
Do you think Yoshino could
have caught a disease
where she's only able to
recognize certain people?
Is that a possibility?
What the hell happened to
that big brain of yours?
If that's the case, we should probably
take her to a hospital, right?
Shut up already!
Maybe a neurosurgeon?
I told you to shut up!
Oof, blood...
Yoshino? You okay?
What are you doing out here?
Gorgeous...
Wait, you can see me?
Of course I can.
Slightly early, but... it's fine.
It's almost seven.
Three days ago, I got home at 7PM.
So I set a reminder for today at 7PM.
Look.
Starts: August 3rd 7:00
Ends: August 6th 7:00
Then... is it over now?
That's gonna depend on you.
Do you even understand what I'm mad about?
Honestly, too many things come to mind...
From now on, you do not contact
Shoma without my permission.
You do not pick fights with him, and if
he starts with you, you don't bite.
Got it?
Got it.
Do you, really?
I'm sorry.
The silent treatment must've
been really effective...
Um, why the silent treatment?
Even when I wanna have
a serious talk with you,
you just offer up an empty apology.
And you're into it when I yell at you,
so what choice do I have
but to not talk to you?
You and Shoma are the only
people I have to do this with.
I'd appreciate if you never
did it again, though.
Are you serious?
Because if you start this kinda crap again,
three days won't be the end of it.
I'm gonna get this in writing, too.
Honestly, how long were
you sitting out here?
I'm not sure... since eight, maybe?
Eight?! Are you outta your mind?
You're gonna make yourself sick.
Just for the record,
the only person you're allowed to drag
into your crap from here on is me.
And I'm not necessarily mad about you
getting Shoma involved in particular.
Do you get that?
What do you mean?
I'm saying whether it's Tsubaki, or one of
your classmates, or even total strangers,
don't pull other people into your bullshit!
Got it?
From now on, if you cause trouble,
or whatever else might happen,
you and I will deal with it ourselves.
Okay. I understand.
Yoshino, you're going to
get wet standing out here.
Hey, what're you...
It's like when the sun goddess came
out from the Ama-no-Iwato cave.
Seeing you again after all this time
has reminded me how beautiful you are.
I could stare at you all day.
What kinda life made you capable of spouting
that kinda flattery with a straight face?
I'm being honest.
And this is the dress
I gave you the other day.
You actually put it on. It looks amazing.
Honestly, you've been so persistent,
I thought coming out looking normal
might piss you off and get me killed.
Figured this might help take the edge off.
You were actually worried about that?
Still, you hardly ever wear the clothes
I buy for you. This is great.
Look, I'm sorry...
I appreciate you getting me stuff, so
I never brought it up before, but...
I tend to like casual clothes like jeans.
That's most of my wardrobe.
Really?
Plus, I don't use most of the gifts
I get, including the ones from you.
I try to keep it all like brand-new
in case I suddenly need to come
up with bail money for you.
And that's only for me?
You haven't said this kind of
thing to anyone else, right?
You're the only dude I anticipate
havin' to sweat the bail money for.
I can think of someone.
What? Is this about Shoma again?
I know how he acts, but Shoma
is doing just fine in life.
That's one thing he's got a whole
hell of an advantage over you on.
I guess you're right.
It's obvious from watching him.
Older people tend to be fond of him
and younger ones look up to him.
He's a hard worker despite how he seems,
so people regardless of age tend to want to
look after him, and he's pretty sociable.
It's almost a talent. He's the
model of a future yakuza.
Uh, so are you.
Hardly. There are certain things that
make you suited to be a yakuza.
I've got none of them.
No one trusts me, and I
don't trust other people.
I don't have any long-term friends,
and other guys are never fond of me.
Which is why I don't intend
to become a yakuza.
Probably couldn't get far if I wanted to.
For someone who doesn't like Shoma, you
sure pay a lot of attention to him.
No matter how much I dislike him, it's
obvious enough from watching him.
He seems to really enjoy being around you.
But for me, our time together is
the only thing I really enjoy.
I can find you no matter where you are,
and you seem to stand out from other people.
It's so strange. It's almost
like you're faintly glowing.
I wonder what it is...
What're you gonna do if you meet someone
you enjoy being around more than me?
Won't happen.
You can't be sure of that.
Have you seriously never had friends before?
What about you, Yoshino?
Did you have friends?
You always turn questions
like this back on me.
I'm honestly curious.
Well, to tell the truth, people tended to talk
about me behind my back in elementary school...
But I had a normal amount of friends.
Until middle school, anyway.
Really?
Some older punks had their eyes on me.
Between my height and my family,
they must've thought I was full of myself.
I'm impressed it didn't set you off.
Wasn't really in a position
to do anything about it.
Besides, partway through first year,
Shoma came around, and from then
on people stayed clear of me.
So, what about you?
I'm not too sure.
I mean, I talked to people...
There was one time, though, that I made
a serious attempt to make friends.
Planned it out pretty thoroughly, even.
Planned it out?
Yeah. But it ultimately didn't
amount to anything.
A real waste of time.
If I had been born somewhere closer
to you, like Toriashi-san...
We could've gone from elementary
school to the same middle school,
and stayed together through
that and high school.
Like childhood friends?
I guess that's what you'd call it.
You're my boyfriend, now, though.
Y'know, you're right. I guess I am.
I'm your boyfriend!
I've been meaning to ask...
what does going out even entail?
Tsubaki said that you're like a pro,
but I don't even know how to hold a ball...
Well, when you really break
it down like that...
Well, can we hold hands?
Right now?
I guess that's fine.
Really?
It's not a big deal. Here.
They're cold. Did the rain give you a chill?
Nah, they're usually like that.
If anything, yours seem kind of hot.
I wonder if you've got a good metabolism...
Are these from stitches?
No. It got infected and went untreated,
so now it just looks like that.
Kinda rough...
Is it uncomfortable?
Sorry, I normally use lotion...
It doesn't hurt or anything, but doesn't
it hurt from being so scratchy?
I've got some hand cream.
Here.
Get the lid.
Hey...!
I don't think this is meant for consumption.
D-D-Dude, what?!
Yeah, sorry. The hand cream just
looked like whipped cream, so...
How fulla shit are you?!
Come up with a better excuse!
I got dressed up because you
mentioned grabbing a parfait!
Cream is the last thing
I wanna see now, though.
No way! Hang on a sec!
Can it! I caught you red-handed!
I'm sorry. I got a little out of control.
Don't suddenly be honest!
Can we please go get parfaits?
That obviously ain't happenin' now!
Osaka: Dump Truck Crashes Into
Kirigaya-gumi-Affiliated Office.
Lieutenant
Somei-gumi Captain
Somei Renji
Lieutenant
Azuma Consortium
Azuma Narumi
Regarding the dump truck that crashed
into a Kirigaya-gumi-affiliated office,
Repayments for Bank System Outage Highest in History
Special Session of the National Diet
Called as Budget Draft Remains Unfinished
Dump Truck Crashed Into Kirigaya-gumi-Affiliated Office
the police have issued a statement
declaring the incident as an accident.
Hope everything's okay.
I can't reach Shoma...
I'm sure he's fine.
How about some personal space over here?
I ain't finalized your contract yet.
You were serious about that?
Damn right I was!
Could we maybe not?
Hello, Shoma?!
Yeah. What's up?
Sorry, were you asleep? You haven't
answered since yesterday, so...
Oh, you saw the news?
It's all right. I don't think
it's gonna amount to much.
Come on, are you serious?
Shoma
I take that to mean it's
already being dealt with?
Can I hang up?
How about you answer my question?
That's enough! Stop talkin'!
Go on, Shoma.
From what I hear, some branch groups
were beefin' over one thing or another.
Like a fight between stupid kids.
The higher-ups are already
takin' care of it.
Since it was a pair of Kirigaya-gumi
affiliates, it's an internal thing.
What do you mean?
The head of the Kirigaya-gumi getting
arrested last month probably indirectly caused it.
Kirigaya-gumi head arrested
Organization effectively leaderless
Breaking News
Kirigaya-gumi Patriarch
Suspect Yatsude Yozo (70)
I did see that on the news,
and had been kinda curious...
That's bound to be it.
How's that?
With the head of the org outta the picture,
the families are getting riled up.
Are things seriously gonna be okay?
Hard to tell.
But that's probably the reason the
boss has been so busy lately.
He's the third from the top, so...
Kiri
Startin' shit over a buncha childish
nonsense... Unbelievable.
It should be taken care of by tomorrow.
It shouldn't have come that.
These guys are under your umbrella.
You oughta have 'em under control.
I'm sorry, sir.
Sorry about dragging you in
for this bullshit, Renji.
Oh, don't worry about me.
Try not to stress out too much about it, sir.
Gotta mind your health.
I guess you got called in for this too, huh?
Hey, it's gotta suck catchin'
shit for what those clowns did!
It's been a while.
How about we grab some drinks?
Knock it off! We ain't kids anymore!
I guess when it comes to booze, you and
Gaku have always been two of a kind.
See ya around.
Shut the hell up.
Azuma
Hello.
Looks like it'll be wrapped up as long as
I deal out the punishment by this weekend.
That's a relief. Don't worry.
Just follow my cues,
and there won't be a problem.
Easily said, but the bastard's
always underfoot.
What do we do? Make a move on him?
Not yet. You leave Renji to me.
And what're you gonna do?
I'll call you back. How's tonight sound?
Fine.
Boss, I've brought the car around.
Sorry, but I think there's
something on your sleeve.
Don't worry. Just some wine stains.
I'll arrange for it to be cleaned, then.
Nah, it's fine.
I was thinking about tossing
this shirt anyway.
Well, damn, you got your ass kicked.
This is what happens when you mess
with a yakuza's granddaughter.
You're too impulsive, man.
Not that I care that much,
as long as I get paid.
What is this?
A flyer.
For Third-Year High School Students and High School Graduates
3rd Mock Entrance Exams
Multiple Choice & Written
I'll take this too.
Certainly.
Can I get one of those in the back?
Oh, sure.
Yoshino, I'm back.
I bought cake.
Shoma